<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_places">Places</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping</string>

    <string name="red_fort"> Red Fort</string>
    <string name="red_fort_description"> The Red Fort is a historic fort in the city of Delhi in India that served as the main residence of the Mughal Emperors.</string>
    <string name="red_fort_location">Netaji Subhash Marg, Lal Qila, Chandni Chowk, New Delhi, Delhi 110006</string>
    <string name="red_fort_timing">9:30 – 16:30</string>

    <string name="humayun_tomb"> Humayun\'s Tomb</string>
    <string name="humayun_tomb_description"> Humayun\'s tomb is the tomb of the Mughal Emperor Humayun in Delhi, India. The tomb was commissioned by Humayun\'s first wife and chief consort, Empress Bega Begum, in 1569–70.</string>
    <string name="humayun_tomb_location">Mathura Road Opposite, Hazrat Nizamuddin Aulia Dargah, Nizamuddin, New Delhi, Delhi 110013</string>
    <string name="humayun_tomb_timing">8:00 – 18:00</string>

    <string name="india_gate"> India Gate</string>
    <string name="india_gate_description"> The India Gate is a war memorial located astride the Rajpath, on the eastern edge of the "ceremonial axis" of New Delhi, formerly called Kingsway.</string>
    <string name="india_gate_location"> Rajpath, India Gate, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="india_gate_timing">7:00 – 23:59</string>

    <string name="jama_masjid"> Jama Masjid</string>
    <string name="jama_masjid_description"> The Masjid e Jahan Numa, commonly known as the Jama Masjid of Delhi, is one of the largest mosques in India. It was built by the Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan between 1650 and 1656 at a cost of one million rupees.</string>
    <string name="jama_masjid_location"> Jama Masjid Rd, Jama Masjid, Chandni Chowk, New Delhi, Delhi 110006</string>
    <string name="jama_masjid_timing">7:00 – 18:30</string>

    <string name="lotus_temple"> Lotus Temple</string>
    <string name="lotus_temple_description"> The Lotus Temple, located in Delhi, India, is a Baháʼí House of Worship that was dedicated in December 1986. Notable for its flowerlike shape, it has become a prominent attraction in the city.</string>
    <string name="lotus_temple_location"> Lotus Temple Rd, Bahapur, Shambhu Dayal Bagh, Kalkaji, New Delhi, Delhi 110019</string>
    <string name="lotus_temple_timing">9:00 – 19:00</string>

</resources>
